pakistan.web.pk 2017-01-21

# Privacy Policy | Pakistan Social Web

Dismiss Notice

Pakistan.web.pk would like to wish Happy Birthday to all its members who celebrate their birthday today __

### What information do we collect?

    We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

    Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

### How do we protect your information?

    We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Do we use cookies?

    Yes. This page explains how this site uses cookies.: Cookie Usage

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

    We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

    This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

    Please visit our Terms of Service and Rules section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms of Service and Rules page.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

    If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will send an email notifying you of any changes.

### Contacting Us

    If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may Contact Us by Clicking Here.

Pakistan Social Web
http://www.pakistan.web.pk
